# **EDUARDO MONDACA**

#### **PORTFOLIO**

https://eduardomondacareyes.github.io/profe ssional-summary/

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Bilingual UxUi Designer with proficient knowledge in design thinking processes for development, deployment and testing of high fidelity functional user-centered interfaces, and HTML and CSS mockups. Experience with Agile methodologies (Design Sprint, Scrum, Kanban) on marketing strategies teams environments focused on user research, creation, design and management of Adwords and Social Ads campaigns.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

# **Prototyping**

Figma	• • • • •
Balsamiq	• • • • •
Sketch	
Adobe XD	• • • • •

Front End	
HTML5	
CSS	• • • • •
Javascript	• • • • •
UX Research	

UX Research	
Google Analytics	
User Persona	••••
Navigation Maps	• • • • •
User Interviews	
Languages	

English	C2
---------	----

# CONTACT



eduardomondacareyes@gmail.com



+56 9 75871125



https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardomondaca-6264721b7/



Lord Cochrane 181 / Depto. 2307 Santiago

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Ux/Ui Designer

# NeoTek Engineering 2020 - 2021

- Research, design, and prototyping of user experience focused interfaces
- Design and creation of UI kits and design systems on
- Full Web Redesign

# **UX and Digital Marketing Specialist**

# Prohabit Real States S.A 2018- 2020

- Developed digital voice and presence for the company
- Administered every stage of digital marketing campaigns of the company, from content creation, design, deployment, data analysis and optimization
- Increased sales by 70% developing digital conversion funnel for sales department
- In charge of copywriting slogans, webpage and corporative documents for the company rebranding
- Community Manager

#### **Startup Project Cofounder**

Satta Project 2014 - 2017

- Creation of brand design and executive development for the project under StartUp Chile sponsorship
- Artistic curatory and technical management of live events produced by Satta Project
- Design and deployment of digital marketing strategies

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Media Communication**

#### DUOC UC

- Professional skill on video edition software (Final Cut X, Premiere, Avid Media Composer) and LDSR cameras and lens kits
- Proficient experience on full audiovisual content production

# **English - Spanish Translation**

#### Universidad de La Serena

- Written and oral English professional skills
- Knowledge and experience on different translations techniques for
- various targets (Marketing, Technical, Literature, Web)
  Simultaneous interpretation experience on business and scholar
- Creation, execution and redaction of live interviews

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- UxUi Design Certification Sence Talento Digital (2021)
- Wordpress Certification Adity Academy (2019)
- Google Adwords Certification (2018)
- TOEIC / Score: 890 (2014)